[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Napoleons suit and socks that he wears to the dance are what colors?", "correct_answer": "brown suit, white socks", "incorrect_answers": ["dark blue suit, white socks", "yellow suit, brown socks", "white suit, black socks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many polar bear subspecies are there?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "5", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the biggest threats to earthworm survival in the UK is the New Zealand Roundworm which feeds on earthworms.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these human physiological properties does the Terminator from the Terminator movies possess?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Bleeding", "Sense of smell", "Sweating"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1921 George Melfords The Sheik debuted and established this star as the cinemas best known lover.", "correct_answer": "Rudolph Valentino", "incorrect_answers": ["George Waggner", "Walter Long", "Frank Butler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first label, which was sewn on the outside of a pair of  jeans in 1936, represented what?", "correct_answer": "A red flag", "incorrect_answers": ["A bear", "A cowboy hat", "A hawk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 6th European Union enlargement took place on May 1 2004. How many countries were admitted then?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "12", "14"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this board game, neither player can see the value of the other players men.", "correct_answer": "Stratego", "incorrect_answers": ["Bridge", "Mille Bournes", "Risk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How fast can a zebra run?", "correct_answer": "40 mph (65 km/h)", "incorrect_answers": ["30 mph (50 km/h)", "25 mph (40 km/h)", "50 mph (80 km/h)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I ran to my room and my daughter brought me a bowl of vegetable soup, but I couldnt eat it due to my phagophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Swallowing", "incorrect_answers": ["Liquids", "Hot objects", "Celery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word atom comes from the Greek atomos which means what?", "correct_answer": "Uncuttable", "incorrect_answers": ["Miniature", "Fast", "Invisible"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What device is used to spy on Istanbuls Soviet Embassy, in James Bonds From Russia With Love?", "correct_answer": "Periscope", "incorrect_answers": ["Tape recorder", "Hidden camera", "Hidden microphone"]}]